YAJNA MATABUDUL

Web Developer

Community Center Lane, Bon Accueil | 59156927 | yajna891@gmail.com

CAREER SUMMARY:

I am a highly enthusiastic and dedicated employee willing to adapt to challenging situations. I believe that I can apply all the knowledge and experiences I have acquired during my course and previous employment to perform well at and be a useful asset to your company.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Lucrin MAURITIUS LTD

Web Developer | March 2022 - Present

- Use of Magento 2 for development
- Use of Salesforce for newsletter creation
- Use of HTML, CSS, JS for front-end development
- Use of PHP for backend development
- Use of sourcetree to interact with Git repositories

Infosys

Systems Engineer | December 2020 - February 2022

- Documentation of existing systems
- Requirement analysis and client liaison
- Development (VueJS, Delphi, C#)
- Testing

Rogers Capital

Trainee Software Engineer | November 2020

- Documentation of existing systems
- Development in C#

LefinTech LTD

Trainee Software Engineer | August 2020 - October 2020

- Maintain web infrastructure on Amazon Cloud
- Develop web front ends in HTML/CSS and JavaScript frameworks
- Implement web backends using REST API and Websockets
- Train machine learning algorithms: data gathering, data cleaning and processing

JEB LTD

Intern Java Developer | May 2020 - June 2020

- Backend Database: Oracle
- Front end development tool: Oracle Apex
- Translator development: Java

Birger

Intern Software Engineer | August 2019 - October 2019

- SQL debugging
- App testing

Starlinks Business Solutions LTD

Intern Web Developer | March 2019 - May 2019

- Creation of websites using Joomla CMS
- Use of Mailchimp for mass emailing
- Documentation on the proper use MS Word, MS Excel, MS
- PowerPoint and computer fundamentals

Nova Interaction

Intern Frontend Web Developer | August 2018 - October 2018

- Content management
- Front-end management
- Back-end management
- Project management

EDUCATION:

2017 - 2020 | Supinfo International University

BSc Computer Science - Engineering

2016 | Droopnath Ramphul State College

Higher School Certificate

2014 | Droopnath Ramphul State College

School Certificate

SKILLS

- Responsive Web Design
- Front End Development
- Time management
- · Working in team

LANGUAGES

- English
- French
- Hindi
- Creol